Guide to the Vassar College Dean of the College, Dean of the Faculty Records, 1917-1997 (bulk 1940-1996
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Educational Testing Service (Box 52)
- Environmental Studies (Box 52)
- Freshman Year (Box 53)
- Funds, Finances (Box 53)
- Graduate Study (Box 53)
- Government Sponsors on Research (Box 53)
- Harvard-Radcliffe (Box 53)
- Health Department (Box 53)
- Hudson River Valley Commission (Box 53)
- Preliminary Studies of Inter-Institution Relationships (Box 53)
- IBM (Box 53)
- Information clippings (Box 53)
- League of Women Voters Membership List (Box 53)
- Liberal Arts Symposium (Box 53)
- Little Report (Box 53)
- Miscellaneous Projects, 1952-1967 (Box 53)
- Middle States Conference - Atlantic City (Box 53)
- [Mills'] Confidential file - (Mill's College Plans) (Box 53)
- Music Department - Committee on New Dimensions (Box 53)
- New York State Teacher's Association Minutes (Box 53)
- NSA Educational Reform Conference (Box 53)
- Office of Education (Box 53)
- Long-Range Planning Committee (Box 53)
- Procedure (Box 53)
- Student Curriculum Committee, 1923-1937, 1949-1958; (4 folders) (Box 53)
- Dean’s Office Furnishing, 1949-1953 (Box 53)
- Education Conference, 1956 (Box 53)
- Executive Committee, 1948-1955 (Box 53)
- Activities of Faculty, 1957-1958 (Box 53)
- Copies from Faculty Minutes, vols. 7 and 8 (Box 53)
- Faculty Replies Re: Fellowships (Box 53)
- Ford Foundation, 1951-1953 (Box 53)
- Committee on Foreign Studies, 1947-1951; (2 folders) (Box 53)
- General Manager, 1935-1953 (Box 53)
- Graduate Studies Inquiries, 1956-1960; (2 folders) (Box 53)
- Faculty, 1949-1958; (4 folders) (Box 53)
- Faculty Children Tuition Plan, 1952-1959 (Box 53)
- Faculty-Trustee-Alumnae Conference Committee, 1952-1957 (Box 53)
- Committee on Fellowships and Graduate Study, 1948-1961 (Box 53)
- CCP Minutes, 1981; (2 folders) (Box 54)
- Curriculum Committee (Box 54)
- Filing (Box 54)
- CCEP – General (Box 54)
- Size of Classes (Box 54)
- Coordinating Committee Minutes, 1952 (Box 54)
- [Field Work, miscellaneous] (Box 54)
- Committee on Student Programs (Box 54)
- [Miscellaneous], 1959-1965 (Box 54)
- Student Filing – Old (Box 54)
- Scholarship Material, 1951-1952 (Box 54)
- Departments, (13 folders) (Box 54)
- Faculty, 1958-1965; (2 folders) (Box 54)
- Student Curriculum Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 54)
- CCP Minutes, 1981-1982; (4 folders) (Box 55)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Annual Reports Dean of the College, 1972-1975; (5 folders) (Box 55)
- Annual Reports Dean of Studies, 1985-1986 (Box 55)
- Salary Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 55)
- Departments Projected 5 year Plan, 1976 (Box 55)
- Committee on New Dimensions, 1967 (Box 55)
- CPC Report and Appendices, 1968; (3 folders) (Box 55)
- Financial Planning Committee, 1975-1976; (2 folders) (Box 55)
- Report of CPC, 1968 (Box 55)
- Report of the President "The New Vassar,", 1964-1970 (Box 55)
- Middle States Vassar Report, 1979 (Box 55)
- CCP, 1977-1978; (3 folders) (Box 55)
- Files [sent] to Storage [in] 1988: Coordinating Committee on Educational Policy, 1957-1959 (Box 56)
- Mrs. Daniels, various notes (Box 56)
- Preliminary Report of Committee on New Dimensions, 1967 (Box 56)
- Statistics on Faculty, 1976-1986 (Box 56)
- Mellon Report, 1959 (Box 56)
- Visits Crump, Venginattis, 1983 (Box 56)
- Brown Foundation Visit (Box 56)
- Committee on Women at Vassar (Box 56)
- Development and National Council (Box 56)
- Trustees - Forward Planning Committee (Box 56)
- Undergraduate Life Committee (Box 56)
- Trustees - Coeducational Committee (Box 56)
- Dean of Faculty Reports to Executive Committee (Box 56)
- Faculty and Studies Committee (Box 56)
- Trustees - General (Box 56)
- Trustees - Faculty and Studies Committee (Box 57)
- Dean of Faculty Reports to Board, 1971; (3 folders) (Box 57)
- Executive Committee (Box 57)
- Committee on Minority Affairs (Box 57)
- Tait's Books and Files, (2 folders) (Box 57)
- Time's Survey Data, 1955 (Box 57)
- CCP minutes, 1953-1958; (12 folders) (Box 57)
- CCP minutes, 1958-1961; (6 folders) (Box 58)
- Report of Joint Trustee- Faculty Committee, 1960 (Box 58)
- Cambridge Associate Report, "A Study of Financial Equilibrium for Vassar,", 1982 (Box 58)
- "A Report of Alternatives from the Committee of New Dimensions,", 1967 (Box 58)
- Board of Trustees, 1948-1981; (7 folders) (Box 58)
- YRO Curricular Planning (Box 58)
- Executive Committee, (3 folders) (Box 58)
- Academic Buildings, 1955-1969 (Box 58)
- American Geography Union (Box 59)
- Association of House Fellows (Box 59)
- Assoc. Colleges of Mid-Hudson Area, 1963-1972; (3 folders) (Box 59)
- Oaths of Allegiance, 1968-1981; (3 folders) (Box 59)
- Admissions (Box 59)
- Alumnae Association, 1970-1974 (Box 59)
- Educational Records Bureau (Box 59)
- Foundation for Integrated Education (Box 59)
- Four School Study (Box 59)
- Fund Raising (Box 59)
- Health and Medical Services (Box 59)
- Institutes, (6 folders) (Box 60)
- Funds, (3 folders) (Box 60)
- Long Range Programs: Committee on Social Action (Box 60)
- Comprehensive Plan Committee, (20 folders) (Box 60)
- Academic Budget (Box 60)
- Environmental Studies (Box 60)
- Institute for Study of Man and His Environment (Box 60)
- Recruit Institute (Box 60)
- Environmental Studies Proposal (Box 60)
- Mid-Hudson Environmental Center (Box 60)
- Clips (Box 60)
- Environmental Studies (Box 60)
- Consultants (Box 61)
- Environmental Studies Background (Box 61)
- Wesleyan Environmental Studies, (14 folders) (Box 61)
- Black Studies, (8 folders) (Box 61)
- Black Studies, (7 folders) (Box 62)
- By-laws (Box 62)
- C. Research Center (Box 62)
- College AAVC Coordination Committee (Box 62)
- Joint Committee (Box 62)
- Joint Committee Documents Relating to Report (Box 62)
- Committee on Master Planning (Box 62)
- Committee on New Dimensions (Box 62)
- Speeches (Box 62)
- Special Projects (Box 62)
- Commencement, 1968; (2 folders) (Box 62)
- Shell Foundation (Box 62)
- Special Students (Box 63)
- Student Activities (Box 63)
- Students - Department Majors (Box 63)
- Faculty Evaluations (Box 63)
- Black Student Housing (Box 63)
- Student Handbooks (Box 63)
- Student Data Base (Box 63)
- Student Body Analysis (Box 63)
- CPC Summer Program (Box 63)
- Summer Use of Campus (Box 63)
- Sunset Lake (Box 63)
- Syllabus (Box 63)
- Teacher Education (Box 63)
- Arlington School District Practice Teaching (Box 63)
- Tenure (Box 63)
- Trustee Committee (Box 63)
- Upward Bound (Box 63)
- Wilderness Workshop (Box 63)
- VP for Student Affairs (Box 63)
- Vassar Farm (Box 63)
- VP for Admission (Box 63)
- Vassar Books (Box 63)
- Studies (Box 63)
- UNESCO (Box 63)
- Bala Jahumpa (Box 63)
- MAT Program (Box 63)
- New Dimensions - Questionnaires (Box 63)
- NY Residence (Box 63)
- Patterns for Progress/Rovetch Report/ Regional Planning (Box 63)
- Pointing of Courses (Box 63)
- Project Changeover (Box 64)
- Roblee-McCarthy Expenditures (Box 64)
- Director of Secondary Education (Box 64)
- Student Interns (Box 64)
- Teacher Education - Fifth Year (Box 64)
- Teacher Education - Five College Project, (2 folders) (Box 64)
- Visitors (Box 64)
- Washington Interns (Vassar-Wellesley), (3 folders) (Box 64)
- Yale-Vassar study (Box 64)
- Physics and Astronomy Annual Reports, 1965-1969 (Box 64)
- Political Science Annual Reports, 1965-1975; (2 folders) (Box 64)
- Psychology Annual Reports, 1965-1969; (1 folder) (Box 64)
- Psychology Annual Reports, 1970-1973; (1 folder) (Box 65)
- STS Annual Reports, 1970 - n.d.; (2 folders) (Box 65)
- Biology, 1965-1976; (2 folders) (Box 65)
- Chemistry (Box 65)
- Computer Science, 1969-1976 (Box 65)
- Coop Bureau of Teachers, Oct 1958 (Box 65)
- CCEP (Box 66)
- DO annual reports, 1949-1961 (Box 65)
- Dean of Studies, July 1961 - June 1971 (Box 65)
- Deans and Deanships, ca. 1950-1959 (Box 65)
- Dean's Program, 1966-1969 (Box 65)
- Dining Facilities (Box 65)
- Elementary Education (Box 65)
- ESA, 1960-1968 (Box 66)
- Dean of the College (Box 66)
- Budgets - Lectures, 1971-1978; (20 folders) (Box 66)
- Academic Buildings, 1970 (Box 66)
- Handicap Access (Box 66)
- Dormitories (Box 66)
- Citizenship Forms (Box 66)
- Biological Science Building, 1964 (Box 66)
- Workload, 1970 (Box 66)
- Library Committee (Box 66)
- Urban Center Review Committee (Box 66)
- Post Office Boxes (Box 66)
- Experimental Lecture Plan (Box 66)
- Budget Sheets, 1979-1980 (Box 66)
- Committee on Higher Education (Box 66)
- Building Repairs, 1977-1978 (Box 66)
- Telephone Changes (Box 66)
- Budget Committee (Box 66)
- Lisle Fellowship, 1978-1979 (Box 67)
- Loyalty Oaths, 1977-1979 (Box 67)
- Henry Luce Foundation Scholar Program, 1973-1978 (Box 67)
- Men's Education, 1967-1968 (Box 67)
- Men's Exchange Programs, 1968 (Box 67)
- Middle states, 1958-1959 (Box 67)
- Mid-Hudson Pattern for Progress, 1978 (Box 67)
- Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 67)
- National Defense Education Act, 1966 (Box 67)
- National Humanities Institute, 1975-1979 (Box 67)
- National Research Council, 1977 (Box 67)
- Nelson Report, 1975 (Box 67)
- NY Public Interest Research Group (NYPIRG), 1978 (Box 67)
- Nursery School, 1962-1979 (Box 67)
- Opening Days (Box 67)
- Project - "Second Chance" (Box 67)
- Registrar, n.d. - 1979 (Box 67)
- Resources, List of Academic Women (Box 67)
- Advanced Committee on Resource Center (Box 67)
- Retrenchment (Box 67)
- Schedule of Classes (Box 67)
- Seven Colleges Conference (Box 67)
- ACMHA, (1 folder) (Box 67)
- ACMHA, (1 folder) (Box 68)
- By-laws Revisions (Box 68)
- College Research Center Reports (Box 68)
- Intercollegiate Resource Center (Box 68)
- Council of Faculty Representatives of NY Colleges, 1971 - n.d. (Box 68)
- Faculty Travel, 1966-1975; (8 folders) (Box 68)
- DOF Requirement, 1970 - n.d. (Box 68)
- Grants - HEW, (3 folders) (Box 68)
- Grants - McCann Estate (Box 68)
- Grants - Federal, 1967-1969; (2 folders) (Box 68)
- Grants - General Foods (Box 68)
- Grants - Higher Education Act, 1965 (Box 68)
- Grants - Higher Education Act, 1963 (Box 68)
- Grants - Higher Education Act Opportunity Program (Box 68)
- Grants - Mudd Foundation (Box 68)
- Grants - NSF, 1968-1970 (Box 68)
- Library (Box 68)
- Miscellaneous: "The River" Course (Box 69)
- Grants - NY State Council on the Arts (Box 69)
- Recorder's Office, (2 folders) (Box 69)
- House Fellows, 1951-1970; (2 folders) (Box 69)
- Department files a-e and all Blegen files: Anthropology/Sociology, 1968-1972, 1976-1979; (8 folders) (Box 69)
- Art, 1976-1979 (Box 69)
- Biology, 1976-1979 (Box 69)
- Chemistry, 1971-1979 (Box 69)
- Classics, 1966-1979 (Box 69)
- Blegen Expenditures, n.d. - 1979 (Box 69)
- Computer Science, 1976-1979 (Box 69)
- Drama, 1972-1979 (Box 69)
- Economics, 1978-1979 (Box 70)
- Education, 1976-1979 (Box 70)
- English, 1976-1979 (Box 70)
- Blegen, (8 folders) (Box 70)
- Psychology - Child Study, 1960-1965 (Box 70)
- Africana Studies, 1972-1979 (Box 70)
- Psychology, 1973-1979; (2 folders) (Box 70)
- Merger of Child Study and Psychology, 1964-1967 (Box 70)
- Keller Plan, 1971-1974 (Box 70)
- SRCD Committee on Film Archives (Box 70)
- Psychology Film Study, 1965-1976 (Box 70)
- Physics/Astronomy, 1970-1979 (Box 70)
- Political Science, 1976-1979 (Box 70)
- Religion, 1976-1979 (Box 70)
- Russian, 1965-1979 (Box 70)
- American Culture, 1976-1979 (Box 71)
- Critical Languages, 1967-1979 (Box 71)
- East Asian, 1976-1979 (Box 71)
- Interdisciplinary Courses: Independent Program, 1962-1979 (Box 71)
- Science, Technology, and Society, 1973-1979 (Box 71)
- Multidisciplinary Studies (Recruitment) (Box 71)
- ACMHA Proposal, 1971 (Box 71)
- Languages, 1962-1979; (4 folders) (Box 71)
- Polish Study, 1968-1976 (Box 71)
- Women's Studies, 1971-1979; (2 folders) (Box 71)
- Grants, 1973-1979; (4 folders) (Box 71)
- Grants, 1974-1979; (17 folders) (Box 72)
- Grants, 1972-1979 (Box 72)
- Grants, 1972-1979; (2 folders) (Box 73)
- Department Chairmen, 1965-1979; (3 folders) (Box 73)
- Black Studies Administration, 1969-1970; (21 folders) (Box 73)
- Black Studies Administration, 1969-1970; (2 folders) (Box 74)
- Black Studies General, 1968-1969; (13 folders) (Box 74)
- Committee on Minority Education (Box 74)
- Area Studies (Box 74)
- French Department, 1965-1979 (Box 74)
- Geology/Geography, 1977-1979 (Box 74)
- German, 1974-1979 (Box 74)
- Hispanic Studies - Vassar/Wesleyan, 1968-1979 (Box 74)
- Hispanic Studies, 1965-1979 (Box 75)
- History, 1973-1979 (Box 75)
- Italian, 1966-1979 (Box 75)
- Math, 1965-1979 (Box 75)
- Music, 1974-1979 (Box 75)
- Physical Education, 1970-1979; (3 folders) (Box 75)
- Ad Hoc Committee on Vassar Athletics, 1978; (2 folders) (Box 75)
- Visiting Committee on Athletics, 1975 (Box 75)
- Black Studies, (2 folders) (Box 75)
- Urban Culture (Box 75)
- Philosophy, 1975-1979 (Box 75)
- Counseling Approach (Box 75)
- Black Studies Clippings (Box 76)
- Curriculum (Box 76)
- Integrated Approach (Box 76)
- Multidisciplinary Studies' Faculty Survey (Box 76)
- Off-Campus Studies [Field Work], 1973-1976 (Box 76)
- Paule Marshall (Box 76)
- Separatist Approach (Box 76)
- Housing and Social Structure (Box 76)
- Faculty Travel, 1975-1977; (2 folders) (Box 76)
- YRO (Box 76)
- Faculty Budgets, 1971-1977; (7 folders) (Box 76)
- Ad-Hoc Faculty Budget Committee (Box 76)
- Res. Committee on Cost of Leaves (Box 76)
- Faculty Leaves, (2 folders) (Box 76)
- Recommendations for Leaves and Promotion, 1968-1971; (3 folders) (Box 76)
- Faculty Load, 1978-1979 (Box 76)
- Student Interns, 1966-1972; (4 folders) (Box 76)
- Student Interns, 1972-1978; (6 folders) (Box 77)
- Faculty Record Cards (Box 77)
- Retirement, (2 folders) (Box 77)
- Salary Scales, 1948-1974; (7 folders) (Box 77)
- Statistics, 1968-1982; (15 folders) (Box 77)
- Secretary of Faculty (Box 77)
- Faculty Research, 1963 (Box 77)
- Faculty Recruitment and Procedures, (4 folders) (Box 78)
- CAC Program (Box 78)
- German (Box 78)
- Physical Education (Box 78)
- Economics, (2 folders) (Box 78)
- Geology and Geography (Box 78)
- English (Box 78)
- Education (Box 78)
- Recruitment and Administrative (Box 78)
- Master Planning, 1969-1976; (4 folders) (Box 78)
- Majors List Committees, 1979-1980; (3 folders) (Box 78)
- Staff Evaluation, (2 folders) (Box 79)
- Faculty Statistics, 1963-1968; (3 folders) (Box 79)
- Suffrage, 1963-1973 (Box 79)
- Tenure, 1980-1981; (3 folders) (Box 79)
- Unemployment Ins., 1980-1981 (Box 79)
- Faculty Unions, 1980-1981 (Box 79)
- Student Advisory Committee (SAC) Material, 1980-1981; (3 folders) (Box 79)
- SAC Revision, 1979-1980 (Box 79)
- SAC Procedures, 1979-1980 (Box 79)
- East Asian Material, (5 folders) (Box 79)
- CAC (Box 79)
- NY State Education - State Aid (Box 79)
- Bundy Plan, 1969 (Box 79)
- Association of [American] Colleges, including Assessment Committee, 1966-1979 (Box 80)
- Academic Calendar, 1971-1979 (Box 80)
- Academic Interns, 1967-1978 (Box 80)
- Academic Resource Center, 1978-1979 (Box 80)
- ACE Questionnaire (Box 80)
- Administrative Retreat (Box 80)
- Staff Meetings (Box 80)
- Advanced Placement (Box 80)
- Affirmative Action Report (Box 80)
- Afro-American Culture Center (Box 80)
- Age Discrimination Act (Box 80)
- Alaska Farm File (Box 80)
- Albany Students, Personnel Interns, 1977 (Box 80)
- Alumnae Reunion, 3 June 1978 (Box 80)
- Alum. Association, 1977-1979 (Box 80)
- Alum. Association of Emeriti (Box 80)
- American Association of University Administration (Box 80)
- AAUP (Box 80)
- AAUW (Box 80)
- ACE, General, 1969-1979 (Box 80)
- ACE, 1978-1979 (Box 80)
- ACE on Int. Personnel (Box 80)
- AC of Learned Societies (Box 80)
- Anglo-American Hellenic Bureau of Education (Box 80)
- Assessment Committee, 1956 (Box 80)
- Assistant to President, 1968-1976 (Box 80)
- Assistant in Instruction and Research Personnel, 1961-1970 (Box 80)
- Associated Colleges of Mid-Hudson Area, 1975-1979 (Box 80)
- Association for Innovation in Higher Education, 1978 (Box 80)
- Association of Colleges and Universities of New York State (Box 80)
- Black Studies - Requests (Box 80)
- Special Services Grant Proposal (Box 80)
- Advising and Tutoring, 1963-1979 (Box 80)
- American Association for Higher Education, 1974-1979 (Box 80)
- Association of American Colleges, 1966-1979 (Box 80)
- Audio Visual Center, 1977-1979 (Box 81)
- Baldridge Reading Program, 1975-1978 (Box 81)
- Coeducation, 1973-1977 (Box 81)
- College Board / Advanced Placement (Box 81)
- Research Committee, 1969 (Box 81)
- Continuing Education (Box 81)
- Aula, 1975-1978 (Box 81)
- Benefit, 1975 (Box 81)
- Berkshire Conference, 1979 (Box 81)
- Bicentennial Commission, 1973-1976 (Box 81)
- Black Political Caucus, 1972-1973 (Box 81)
- Blacks and the Law Course, 1979 (Box 81)
- BOCES, 1962-1969 (Box 81)
- Brookings Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 81)
- Buckley Amm., 1974-1978 (Box 81)
- Buildings and Grounds, 1974 (Box 81)
- Calendar, 1970-1979 (Box 81)
- Evelyn Wood Reading Dynamics Institute (Box 81)
- Campus Facilities, 1967-1976 (Box 81)
- Carnegie Comm., 1973-1974 (Box 81)
- Cary Estate - N.Y. Botanical Gardens, 1972-1975 (Box 81)
- Catalogue, 1967-1979 (Box 81)
- Central Administration (Box 81)
- Chaplain (Box 81)
- Charter, 1968-1969 (Box 81)
- Chataqua Institution (Box 81)
- Citizens' Board, 1973 (Box 81)
- Class Size Study, 1973-1974 (Box 81)
- Clearing House on Higher Education, 1976 (Box 81)
- Coalition for Social Responsibility, 1978 (Box 81)
- College Center and Campus Activities, 1974-1976 (Box 81)
- College Policy, 1976-1979 (Box 81)
- College Store, 1973-1976 (Box 81)
- Commencement, 1975-1979 (Box 81)
- Columbia University Institute of Human Nutrition, 1975 (Box 81)
- Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1971-1978; (2 folders) (Box 81)
- Comptroller, 1965-1979 (Box 81)
- Concerns, 1977-1978 (Box 82)
- Conservation - Putnam Fund, 1965-1972 (Box 82)
- Payroll and Personnel etc., 1978-1981; (4 folders) (Box 82)
- Dean of Faculty - Office Procedure (Box 82)
- FASC Studies (Box 82)
- Reappointments of Assistant Professors, 1973-1977 (Box 82)
- AAUP Reported Average Salaries by Rank (Box 82)
- Alan Simpson's 13 Year Report (Box 82)
- Ad hoc Committee Policy (Box 82)
- Faculty Reviews and Promotions, (11 folders) (Box 82)
- Affirmative Action - Individuals, (2 folders) (Box 82)
- Committee Academic Panel (Box 82)
- Faculty - Anti-Nepotism (Box 82)
- Faculty Appeal Committee (Box 82)
- Faculty Budget, 1978-1982; (6 folders) (Box 82)
- Faculty Benefits, (9 folders) (Box 83)
- Faculty Clubs (Box 83)
- Faculty Contracts, (2 folders) (Box 83)
- Faculty Development (Box 83)
- Faculty Count (Box 83)
- Faculty Distinctions and Awards (Box 83)
- Faculty Employment (Box 83)
- Affirmative Action (Box 83)
- Faculty Employment Practices, 1972-1974 (Box 83)
- Faculty Exchange Programs (Box 83)
- FASC (Box 83)
- Faculty Files, Access to (Box 83)
- Faculty Handbook, 1972-1982; (5 folders) (Box 83)
- Faculty Leaves, 1966-1981; (2 folders) (Box 83)
- Faculty Lounge (Box 83)
- Faculty Lists, (2 folders) (Box 83)
- Faculty Maternity (Box 83)
- Faculty Meetings and Minutes, 1968-1979; (3 folders) (Box 83)
- Faculty Meetings and Minutes, 1966-1968 (Box 84)
- Faculty, miscellaneous (Box 84)
- Faculty - New Appointments (Box 84)
- Faculty - Outside Professional Activities (Box 84)
- Faculty - Part-Time (Box 84)
- Faculty - Personnel Form (Box 84)
- Retired Faculty - Professorships (Box 84)
- Professional - Non-Faculty Materials (Box 84)
- Faculty Publications (Box 84)
- Faculty Questionnaires (Box 84)
- Faculty Rank (Box 84)
- Continuing Education, 1963-1979; (2 folders) (Box 84)
- Convocation, 1968-1979 (Box 84)
- Cost of Instruction, 1979 (Box 84)
- Course Credit, 1972-1973 (Box 84)
- Course Numbering, 1971 (Box 84)
- Council on Environmental Concern (Box 84)
- Danforth Foundation, 1959-1979; (2 folders) (Box 84)
- Day Care Center Proposal, 1977-1978 (Box 84)
- DOF Acknowledgements, 1972-1978 (Box 84)
- DOF, 1967-1979 (Box 84)
- Dean of Freshmen, 1967-1979 (Box 84)
- Dean's Houseguests (Box 84)
- Dean of Studies, 1976-1979 (Box 84)
- Department of Halls, 1974-1979 (Box 84)
- Development Office, 1973-1979 (Box 84)
- Office of Educational Services, 1974-1979 (Box 84)
- Director of Residences, 1967-1979 (Box 84)
- Discretionary Funds, 1967-1969 (Box 84)
- Distribution Requirements, 1971-1974 (Box 85)
- Editorial Services, 1978 (Box 85)
- Educational Technology, 1967-1974; (3 folders) (Box 85)
- Election of Courses, 1959-1974 (Box 85)
- Educational Testing Service, 1971-1979 (Box 85)
- Employee Privacy, 1976 (Box 85)
- Energy Crisis, 1973-1975 (Box 85)
- Enrollment, 1953-1979 (Box 85)
- Equipment Inventory, 1956-1969; (2 folders) (Box 85)
- Equal Opportunity, 1977-1979 (Box 85)
- Esso Educational Foundation, 1967-1972 (Box 85)
- Exchange Program - 12 College, 1969-1978 (Box 85)
- Examinations, 1959-1979 (Box 85)
- Exchange Program - Marist College, 1972-1976 (Box 85)
- Student Exchange Program, 1967-1979 (Box 85)
- Experiment in International Living (Box 85)
- Experimental College, 1976 (Box 85)
- Faculty Candidates, 1965-1979 (Box 85)
- Faculty Mailings, 1975-1979 (Box 85)
- Fees, 1961-1979 (Box 85)
- Field Work - Student Transportation, 1965-1968 (Box 85)
- Financial Aid, 1967-1979 (Box 85)
- Ford Foundation - Parents' College Plans - Miscellaneous, 1959 (Box 85)
- Ford Profile, 1961-1971 (Box 85)
- Foreign Students, 1965-1970 (Box 85)
- Dickensen-Kayden Fund D48 (Box 85)
- Emily Delafiels Floyd Fund (Box 85)
- Matz Gift (Box 85)
- Jeanne R. Low Fund (Box 85)
- Funds in Trust - Gifts, 1966-1978 (Box 85)
- Budget and Discretionary Funds, 1966-1970 (Box 85)
- Fun File, 1976 (Box 85)
- Future Uses of Main Building (Box 85)
- Government Agencies Communiqué, 1975-1979 (Box 85)
- Government Funding Resources, 1978 (Box 85)
- Governance Revision, 1968-1979 (Box 85)
- Graduation Requirements (Box 85)
- Grades - The Hedgerows in England (Box 85)
- New Dimensions, (2 folders) (Box 86)
- Yale-Vassar Study, (7 folders) (Box 86)
- Bowdoin Conference (Box 86)
- CCEP Report (Box 86)
- Evaluation Report, 1958 (Box 86)
- Joint Trustee-Administration-Faculty Committee, 1959-1961 (Box 86)
- CPC Grading (Box 86)
- CPC Units - Credits (Box 86)
- Curriculum Committee Provisional Grades (Box 86)
- CPC Evaluation (Box 86)
- Course Numberings (Box 86)
- Grades, 1966-1979 (Box 86)
- Graduate Study at Vassar College, 1960-1979 (Box 86)
- Graduate Study by Vassar College's Students at Other Institutions, 1958-1969 (Box 86)
- Graduate Study, 1971-1973 (Box 86)
- Graduate Study Inquiries, 1963-1970 (Box 86)
- Growth of College, 1972 (Box 86)
- Guide for College Grads, 1975 (Box 86)
- Ad-hoc Committee - Faculty By-Laws, 1969; (2 folders) (Box 87)
- Miscellaneous [Personnel], (2 folders) (Box 87)
- CCP - Minutes (Box 87)
- CCP, 1969 (Box 87)
- CCP, (2 folders) (Box 87)
- Miscellaneous, (8 folders) (Box 87)
- Miscellaneous, (4 folders) (Box 88)
- Graduate Center, 1969-1971; (3 folders) (Box 88)
- IBM Grant for Science and Engineering (Box 88)
- Steering Committee - Plan Function (Box 88)
- Steering Committee - Student Committee (Box 88)
- Student Power (Box 88)
- Recruitment - Coordinate College (Box 88)
- Recruitment - Institution Study of Teaching (Box 88)
- Classrooms Syracuse University (Box 88)
- Research Proposals - Chapman (Box 88)
- Science and Engineering - New York State (Box 88)
- MAT, (2 folders) (Box 88)
- MAT, (16 folders) (Box 89)
- Graduate Center, 1971-1972 (Box 89)
- CPC Notes (Box 89)
- Fellowship and Graduate Study Commission, (3 folders) (Box 89)
- Classrooms - Union College (Box 89)
- Wesleyan - Coordinate College (Box 89)
- Men's Education (Box 89)
- MSA, (2 folders) (Box 89)
- Material on Federal Grants, Loans, etc. (Box 89)
- Marion Tait - Personal (Box 90)
- Students, (4 folders) (Box 90)
- Under-Elected Courses (Box 90)
- Urban Teachers' Corp Programs (Box 90)
- Summer Program for Disadvantaged (Box 90)
- Student Drop-In Center (Box 90)
- "Springside" (Box 90)
- Special Projects, 1970-1973; (2 folders) (Box 90)
- Alan Simpson, President, (3 folders) (Box 90)